collegedudes247.com 2009-12-21

# CollegeDudes247: Naked College Men, Amateur Hot Guys, Horny Boys, Big Cock, Hardcore Gay Sex

February 4, 2008

Collegedudes247.com recognizes that privacy is important. This document discusses the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use collegedudes247.com, as well as the actions we take to safeguard your information.

**Personal Information**  

* Collegedudes247.com collects limited personal information when you become a member or otherwise interact with us. "Personal information" is information that you provide to us or our business partners which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information. We **will not** provide your personal information to third parties except for billing or other necessary business and legal purposes. 
* Collegedudes247.com uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use collegedudes247.com in order to improve the quality of our services.
* Our servers may automatically record information when you visit our website, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

**Data Uses**  

* We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 
* We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve collegedudes247.com. 
* We may share aggregated **non-personal information** with third parties. 
* We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud, or ensuring the security of our infrastructure. 
* When you send email or other communication to collegedudes247.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**Your choices**  

* You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 
* We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

If you have additional questions, please contact us any time at aaron@collegedudes247.com
